Cope, Elmer F. Papers on Microfilm 5862 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 1950-1951 Press releases 1950-1951 Economic stabilization to Feb-Mar 1951 (Reel 26)
  - Economic stabilization, 1950-1951; 2 (Reel 26)
    Box 37: Folder 5. December 7, 1950 - June 20, 1951
  - General, 1950; 3 (Reel 26)
    Box 37: Folder 6. Uncertain dates
  - Clippings, 1950; 4 (Reel 26)
    Box 37: Folder 7. January-March, 1950
  - Clippings, 1950; 5 (Reel 26)
    Box 38: Folder 1. April-May, 1950
  - Clippings, 1950; 6 (Reel 26)
    Box 38: Folder 2. June-December, 1950
  - General, 1951; 7 (Reel 26)
    Box 38: Folder 3. January 1-February 19, 1951
  - ICFTU Emergency Committee meeting, Brussels, 1951; 8 (Reel 26)
    Box 38: Folder 4. February 20-23, 1951
  - General, 1951; 9 (Reel 26)
    Box 38: Folder 5. February 20-March 31, 1951
- Apr 1951 to Feb 1952 (Reel 27)
  - General, 1951; 1 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 1. April 1-July 4, 1951
  - General, 1951; 2 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 2. July 5-December 31, 1951
  - Cope's folders; CIO releases, 1951; 3 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 3. January 19-June 15, 1951
  - Textile Workers Union, 1951; 4 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 4. February 21, 1951
  - Wage stabilization #1, 1951; 5 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 5. February-April, 1951
  - Wage stabilization #2, 1951; 6 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 6. February-April, 1951
  - United Labor Policy Committee, 1951; 7 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 7. February-April, 1951
  - ICFTU Executive Board, 1951; 8 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 8. February 20-April 20, 1951
  - CIO Councils (Pennsylvania), 1951; 9 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 9. February-Ma, 1951
  - Transport Service Employees, 1951; 10 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 10. March, 1951
  - CIO Executive Board, 1951; 11 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 11. March 15-16, 1951
  - Vic Reuther, 1951; 12 (Reel 27)
    Box 39: Folder 12. March-April, 1951
  - Cope's folders; United Steelworkers of America circulars etc., 1951; 13 (Reel 27)
    Box 40: Folder 1. March-May, 1951
  - Conventions, 1951; 14 (Reel 27)
    Box 40: Folder 2. March 30-June 1, 1951
  - ICFTU correspondence, 1951; 15 (Reel 27)
    Box 40: Folder 3. April, 1951
  - Midwest Worker Education Conference, 1951; 16 (Reel 27)
    Box 40: Folder 4. February-April, 1951
  - Revolutions, 1951; 17 (Reel 27)
    Box 40: Folder 5. April, 1951
  - General, 1952; 18 (Reel 27)
    Box 40: Folder 6. January-February, 1952
- Feb 1952 to May 1953 (Reel 28)
  - Iron ore case, 1952; 1 (Reel 28)
    Box 40: Folder 7. February, 1952
  - General, 1952; 2 (Reel 28)
    Box 40: Folder 8. March-April, 1952
  - ICFTU, 1952; 3 (Reel 28)
    Box 40: Folder 9. March 14-19, 1952
  - General, 1952; 4 (Reel 28)
    Box 41: Folder 1. May, 1952
  - General, 1952; 5 (Reel 28)
    Box 41: Folder 2. June-December, 1952
  - Clippings, 1952; 6 (Reel 28)
    Box 41: Folder 3.
  - General, 1953; 7 (Reel 28)
    Box 41: Folder 4. January-April, 1953
  - General, 1953; 8 (Reel 28)
    Box 41: Folder 5. May, 1953
  - Venezuela trip-background material, 1953; 9 (Reel 28)
    Box 41: Folder 6. May, 1953
  - Venezuela trip - other material, 1953; 10 (Reel 28)
    Box 41: Folder 7. May, 1953
- Jun 1953 to Jan 1954 (Reel 29)
  - General, 1953; 1 (Reel 29)
    Box 42: Folder 1. June-September, 1953
  - Canadian negotiations, 1953; 2 (Reel 29)
    Box 42: Folder 2. June-November, 1953
  - General, 1953; 3 (Reel 29)
    Box 42: Folder 3. October, 1953
  - General, 1953; 4 (Reel 29)
    Box 42: Folder 4. November, 1953
  - General, 1953; 5 (Reel 29)
    Box 42: Folder 5. December, 1953
  - Clippings, 1953; 6 (Reel 29)
    Box 43: Folder 1.
  - General, 1954; 7 (Reel 29)
    Box 43: Folder 2. January, 1954
- Feb 1954 to Nov 1954 (Reel 30)
  - General, 1954; 1 (Reel 30)
    Box 43: Folder 3. February 1-15, 1954
  - General, 1954; 2 (Reel 30)
    Box 43: Folder 4. February 15-28, 1954
  - General, 1954; 3 (Reel 30)
    Box 43: Folder 5. March 1-April 15, 1954
  - General, 1954; 4 (Reel 30)
    Box 44: Folder 1. April 16-30, 1954
  - General, 1954; 5 (Reel 30)
    Box 44: Folder 2. May, 1954
  - General, 1954; 6 (Reel 30)
    Box 44: Folder 3. June, 1954
  - General, 1954; 7 (Reel 30)
    Box 44: Folder 4. July, 1954
  - General, 1954; 8 (Reel 30)
    Box 44: Folder 5. August-October, 1954
  - General, 1954; 9 (Reel 30)
    Box 45: Folder 1. November, 1954
- Dec 1954 to Sep 1955 (Reel 31)
  - General, 1954; 1 (Reel 31)
    Box 45: Folder 2. December, 1954
  - Clippings, 1954; 2 (Reel 31)
    Box 45: Folder 3.
  - General, 1955; 3 (Reel 31)
    Box 45: Folder 4. January 1-14, 1955
  - General, 1955; 4 (Reel 31)
    Box 46: Folder 1. January 15-31, 1955
  - General, 1955; 5 (Reel 31)
    Box 46: Folder 2. February-April, 1955
  - General, 1955; 6 (Reel 31)
    Box 46: Folder 3. May-August, 1955
  - General, 1955; 7 (Reel 31)
    Box 46: Folder 4. September, 1955
- Oct 1955 to Apr 1956 (Reel 32)
  - General, 1955; 1 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 1. October, 1955
  - UNESCO - Cincinnati, 1955; 2 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 2. November 3-5, 1955
  - General, 1955; 3 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 3. November 6-13, 1955
  - Cope's work on Pres. D.J. McDonald's statement on foreign economic policy, 1955; 4 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 4. November 14, 1955
  - Joint Committee on Economic Report hearings on foreign economic policy, 1955; 5 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 5. November 14, 1955
  - General, 1955; 6 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 6. November 15-December 31, 1955
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1955; 7 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 7.
  - Clippings, 1955; 8 (Reel 32)
    Box 47: Folder 8.
  - General, 1956; 9 (Reel 32)
    Box 48: Folder 1. January, 1956
  - General, 1956; 10 (Reel 32)
    Box 48: Folder 2. February-March, 1956
  - General, 1956; 11 (Reel 32)
    Box 48: Folder 3. April-May, 1956
  - Labrador iron ore, 1956; 12 (Reel 32)
    Box 48: Folder 4. April-August, 1956
  - The church and economic life, 1956; 13 (Reel 32)
    Box 48: Folder 5. April 12-15, 1956
- May-Dec 1956 to Clippings + leaflets, Jan-Mar 1956 (Reel 33)
  - Europe, 1956; 1 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 1. May, 1956
  - General, 1956; 2 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 2. June, 1956
  - General, 1956; 3 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 3. July-August, 1956
  - General, 1956; 4 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 4. September, 1956
  - Committee for a National Economic Policy - Sub-committee on Tariffs and Reciprocal Trade Agreements, 1956; 5 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 5. September-December, 1956
  - United Steelworkers Convention, 1956; 6 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 6. September 17-21, 1956
  - meeting of Dept. of Church and Economic Life, Nat'l Council of Churches, 1956; 7 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 7. October, 1956
  - General, 1956; 8 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 8. October-December
  - Miscellaneous, 1956; 9 (Reel 33)
    Box 49: Folder 9. Undated
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1956; 10 (Reel 33)
    Box 50: Folder 1.
  - Clippings, 1956; 11 (Reel 33)
    Box 50: Folder 2. January, 1956
  - Clippings and leaflets, 1956; 12 (Reel 33)
    Box 50: Folder 3. February-March, 1956
- Apr 1956 to Mar 1957 (Reel 34)
  - Clippings and leaflets, 1956; 1 (Reel 34)
    Box 50: Folder 4. April-June, 1956
  - Clippings and leaflets, 1956; 2 (Reel 34)
    Box 50: Folder 5. July-August, 1956
  - Clippings and leaflets, 1956; 3 (Reel 34)
    Box 50: Folder 6. September-December, 1956
  - General, 1957; 4 (Reel 34)
    Box 51: Folder 1. January, 1957
  - IMF correspondence, 1957; 5 (Reel 34)
    Box 51: Folder 2. January-September, 1957
  - General, 1957; 6 (Reel 34)
    Box 51: Folder 3. February, 1957
  - Foreign wire products import problem, 1957; 7 (Reel 34)
    Box 51: Folder 4. March-October, 1957
  - General, 1957; 8 (Reel 34)
    Box 51: Folder 5. March, 1957
- Apr 1957 to June 1957 (Reel 35)
  - General, 1957; 1 (Reel 35)
    Box 51: Folder 6. April, 1957
  - IMF, 1957; 2 (Reel 35)
    Box 52: Folder 1. April-September, 1957
  - Lead-zinc situation, 1957; 3 (Reel 35)
    Box 52: Folder 2. April-November, 1957
  - General, 1957; 4 (Reel 35)
    Box 52: Folder 3. May, 1957
  - General, 1957; 5 (Reel 35)
    Box 52: Folder 4. June 1-12, 1957
  - International Labor Organization (ILO) conference, Geneva, 1957; 6 (Reel 35)
    Box 53: Folder 1. June, 1957
- Jun 1957 to Dec 1957 (Reel 36)
  - General, 1957; 1 (Reel 36)
    Box 53: Folder 2. June 13-July 18, 1957
  - General, 1957; 2 (Reel 36)
    Box 53: Folder 3. August-September, 1957
  - Merrill Center for Economics, 1957; 3 (Reel 36)
    Box 53: Folder 4. August 5-16, 1957
  - IMF meeting, Lugnano, Italy, 1957; 4 (Reel 36)
    Box 54: Folder 1. September 17-19, 1957
  - General, 1957; 5 (Reel 36)
    Box 54: Folder 2. October, 1957
  - National Council of Churches, Dept. of Church and Economic Life, 10th anniversary program, 1957; 6 (Reel 36)
    Box 54: Folder 3. October 2-5, 1957h anniversary program
  - ILO Iron and Steel Conference, Monterrey, Mexico, 1957; 7 (Reel 36)
    Box 54: Folder 4. October 7-18, 1957
  - General, 1957; 8 (Reel 36)
    Box 54: Folder 5. November-December, 1957
- 1957 undated items to Apr 1958 United Steelworkers addresses (Reel 37)
  - Undated items, 1957; 1 (Reel 37)
    Box 55: Folder 1.
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1957; 2 (Reel 37)
    Box 55: Folder 2.
  - Clippings, 1957; 3 (Reel 37)
    Box 55: Folder 3.
  - General, 1958; 4 (Reel 37)
    Box 55: Folder 4. January, 1958
  - National Council of Churches, Dept. of Church and Economic Life, General Committee meeting, 1958; 5 (Reel 37)
    Box 56: Folder 1. January 17, 1958
  - Iron ore - Alabama, Michigan, Minnesota; non-ferrous metals, 1958; 6 (Reel 37)
    Box 56: Folder 2. January-March, 1958
  - Foreign affairs, 1958; 7 (Reel 37)
    Box 56: Folder 3. January-April Foreign affairs
  - United Steelworkers - Pres. McDonald's addresses and directives, 1958; 8 (Reel 37)
    Box 56: Folder 4. January-April, 1958
- Feb 1958 to Sep 1958 (Reel 38)
  - Caracas (Venezuela) trips and backgrounds, 1958; 1 (Reel 38)
    Box 56: Folder 5. February 2, 1958
  - General, 1958; 2 (Reel 38)
    Box 56: Folder 6. February 3-16, 1958
  - General, 1958; 3 (Reel 38)
    Box 56: Folder 7. February 16-28, 1958
  - General, 1958; 4 (Reel 38)
    Box 57: Folder 1. March-May, 1958
  - Ohio employment statistics, 1958; 5 (Reel 38)
    Box 57: Folder 2. April-July, 1958
  - OSU Labor Advisory Committee, 1958; 6 (Reel 38)
    Box 57: Folder 3. May and November, 1958
  - General, 1958; 7 (Reel 38)
    Box 57: Folder 4. June, 1958
  - General, 1958; 8 (Reel 38)
    Box 57: Folder 5. July-August, 1958
  - General, 1958; 9 (Reel 38)
    Box 57: Folder 6. September, 1958
- Oct 1958 to 1958 Anti-Right-to-Work materials (Reel 39)
  - General, 1958; 1 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 1. October, 1958
  - Bricker, O'Neill statements, 1958; 2 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 2. October 18 and 21, 1958
  - General, 1958; 3 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 3. November-December, 1958
  - Pro-Right-to-Work material - out of state, 1958; 4 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 4.
  - Pro-Right-to-Work material - Ohio, 1958; 5 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 5.
  - Right-to-Work states - especially Indiana, 1958; 6 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 6.
  - Right-to-Work backers - data about, 1958; 7 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 7.
  - Anti-Right-to-Work supporters, 1958; 8 (Reel 39)
    Box 58: Folder 8.
  - Anti-Right-to-Work advertisements, 1958; 9 (Reel 39)
    Box 59: Folder 1.
  - Anti-Right-to-Work literature, 1958; 10 (Reel 39)
    Box 59: Folder 2.
  - Anti-Right-to-Work materials, 1958; 11 (Reel 39)
    Box 59: Folder 3.
- 1958 Anti-Right-to-Work materials to 1958 Boy Scouts (Reel 40)
  - Anti-Right-to-Work materials - Ohio, 1958; 1 (Reel 40)
    Box 59: Folder 4.
  - Anti-Right-to-Work materials - from religious leaders, 1958; 2 (Reel 40)
    Box 59: Folder 5.
  - Negro Right-to-Work, 1958; 3 (Reel 40)
    Box 60: Folder 1.
  - Right-to-Work farmers, 1958; 4 (Reel 40)
    Box 60: Folder 2.
  - Anti-Right-to-Work speech texts, 1958; 5 (Reel 40)
    Box 60: Folder 3.
  - Right-to-Work clippings, 1958; 6 (Reel 40)
    Box 60: Folder 4. June-October 15, 1958
  - Right-to-Work clippings, 1958; 7 (Reel 40)
    Box 60: Folder 5. October 16-December 14, 1958
  - Church and economic life (National Council of Churches), 1958; 8 (Reel 40)
    Box 61: Folder 1. January-May, 1958
  - Church and economic life (National Council of Churches), 1958; 9 (Reel 40)
    Box 61: Folder 2. June-October, 1958
  - Boy Scouts, 1958; 10 (Reel 40)
    Box 61: Folder 3.
- 1958 Clippings to Papers Nov 1959 (Reel 41)
  - Clippings, 1958; 1 (Reel 41)
    Box 61: Folder 4.
  - Calendars, 1959; 2 (Reel 41)
    Box 61: Folder 5.
  - General, 1959; 3 (Reel 41)
    Box 62: Folder 1. January, 1959
  - General, 1959; 4 (Reel 41)
    Box 62: Folder 2. February-March, 1959
  - General, 1959; 5 (Reel 41)
    Box 62: Folder 3. April-June, 1959
  - General, 1959; 6 (Reel 41)
    Box 62: Folder 4. July-August, 1959
  - General, 1959; 7 (Reel 41)
    Box 62: Folder 5. September-November, 1959
- Dec 1959 to Mar 1960 (Reel 42)
  - General, 1959; 1 (Reel 42)
    Box 63: Folder 1. December, 1959
  - General, 1959; 2 (Reel 42)
    Box 63: Folder 2. Undated
  - Boy Scouts, 1959; 3 (Reel 42)
    Box 63: Folder 3.
  - Clippings, 1959; 4 (Reel 42)
    Box 63: Folder 4.
  - General, 1960; 5 (Reel 42)
    Box 63: Folder 5. January, 1960
  - COPE (Committee on Political Education) meeting, 1960; 6 (Reel 42)
    Box 64: Folder 1. January 12, 1960
  - General, 1960; 7 (Reel 42)
    Box 64: Folder 2. February, 1960
  - COPE (Committee on Political Education) meetings, 1960; 8 (Reel 42)
    Box 64: Folder 3. February, 1960
  - General, 1960; 9 (Reel 42)
    Box 64: Folder 4. March, 1960
- Apr 1960 to Jan 1961 (Reel 43)
  - Civil rights conference, Columbus, Ohio, 1960; 1 (Reel 43)
    Box 64: Folder 5. April 1-2, 1960
  - General, 1960; 2 (Reel 43)
    Box 64: Folder 6. April, 1960
  - General, 1960; 3 (Reel 43)
    Box 65: Folder 1. May-June, 1960
  - General, 1960; 4 (Reel 43)
    Box 65: Folder 2. July-August, 1960
  - General, 1960; 5 (Reel 43)
    Box 65: Folder 3. September-November 10, 1960
  - General, 1960; 6 (Reel 43)
    Box 65: Folder 4. November 11-December 31, 1960
  - General, 1960; 7 (Reel 43)
    Box 65: Folder 5. Undated
  - Clippings, 1960; 8 (Reel 43)
    Box 66: Folder 1.
  - General, 1961; 9 (Reel 43)
    Box 66: Folder 2.
- Feb 1961 to Oct 1961 (Reel 44)
  - General, 1961; 1 (Reel 44)
    Box 66: Folder 3. February 1-March 15, 1961
  - General, 1961; 2 (Reel 44)
    Box 66: Folder 4. March 16-April 31, 1961
  - General, 1961; 3 (Reel 44)
    Box 66: Folder 5. May, 1961
  - General, 1961; 4 (Reel 44)
    Box 67: Folder 1. June, 1961
  - General, 1961; 5 (Reel 44)
    Box 67: Folder 2. July-September, 1961
  - General, 1961; 6 (Reel 44)
    Box 67: Folder 3. October, 1961
  - Church and economic life (National Council of Churches), 1961; 7 (Reel 44)
    Box 67: Folder 4. October 6-8 (also March-December), 1961
- Nov 1961 to Jan 1962 (Reel 45)
  - General, 1961; 1 (Reel 45)
    Box 68: Folder 1. November-December, 1961
  - Economic growth, 1961; 2 (Reel 45)
    Box 68: Folder 2. November, 1961
  - Ohio Council on Economic Education, 1961; 3 (Reel 45)
    Box 68: Folder 3. February-December, 1961
  - General, 1961; 4 (Reel 45)
    Box 68: Folder 4. Undated
  - Clippings, 1961; 5 (Reel 45)
    Box 68: Folder 5.
  - General, 1962; 6 (Reel 45)
    Box 69: Folder 1. January 1-17, 1962
  - General, 1962; 7 (Reel 45)
    Box 69: Folder 2. January18-31, 1962
- Feb 1962 to Sep 1962 (Reel 46)
  - General, 1962; 1 (Reel 46)
    Box 69: Folder 3. February, 1962
  - General, 1962; 2 (Reel 46)
    Box 69: Folder 4. March, 1962
  - General, 1962; 3 (Reel 46)
    Box 70: Folder 1. April, 1962
  - General, 1962; 4 (Reel 46)
    Box 70: Folder 2. May, 1962
  - General, 1962; 5 (Reel 46)
    Box 70: Folder 3. June-July, 1962
  - General, 1962; 6 (Reel 46)
    Box 70: Folder 4. August-September, 1962
- Oct-Dec 1962, Undated items, 1962 to Jan-Oct 1962 Ohio Council Economic Education (Reel 47)
  - General, 1962; 1 (Reel 47)
    Box 71: Folder 1. October-November, 1962
  - National Council of Churches, Pittsburgh Conference, 1962; 2 (Reel 47)
    Box 71: Folder 2. November 8-11, 1962
  - General, 1962; 3 (Reel 47)
    Box 71: Folder 3. December 1-15, 1962
  - General, 1962; 4 (Reel 47)
    Box 71: Folder 4. December 16-31, 1962
  - General, 1962; 5 (Reel 47)
    Box 71: Folder 5.
  - Foreign trade bill and Common Market, 1962; 6 (Reel 47)
    Box 71: Folder 6. January-November, 1962
  - Ohio Council of Economic Education, 1962; 7 (Reel 47)
    Box 72: Folder 1. January-October, 1962
- Jan 1962 clippings to Papers Apr 1963 (Reel 48)
  - Clippings, 1962; 1 (Reel 48)
    Box 72: Folder 2. January-September, 1962
  - Clippings, 1962; 2 (Reel 48)
    Box 72: Folder 3. October-December, 1962
  - General, 1963; 3 (Reel 48)
    Box 72: Folder 4. January, 1963
  - William Green Scholarship Committee, 1963; 4 (Reel 48)
    Box 72: Folder 5. January-May, 1963
  - Ohio Council on Economic Education, 1963; 5 (Reel 48)
    Box 73: Folder 1. January-November, 1963
  - General, 1962; 6 (Reel 48)
    Box 73: Folder 2. February, 1963
  - General, 1963; 7 (Reel 48)
    Box 73: Folder 3. March, 1963
  - General, 1963; 8 (Reel 48)
    Box 73: Folder 4. April, 1963
- Apr 1963 to Feb 1964 (Reel 49)
  - Indiana University project, 1963; 1 (Reel 49)
    Box 74: Folder 1. April-October, 1963
  - National Council of Churches, 1963; 2 (Reel 49)
    Box 74: Folder 2. April-December, 1963
  - General, 1963; 3 (Reel 49)
    Box 74: Folder 3. May-June, 1963
  - General, 1963; 4 (Reel 49)
    Box 74: Folder 4. July-October 20, 1963
  - Steelworker correspondence, 1963; 5 (Reel 49)
    Box 74: Folder 5. September-October, 1963
  - General, 1963; 6 (Reel 49)
    Box 75: Folder 1. October 21-November 30, 1963
  - Indiana University. Resident Labor Education program, 1963-1964; 7 (Reel 49)
    Box 75: Folder 2. November, 1963-February, 1964
- Dec 1963 to Jun 1964 (Reel 50)
  - General, 1963; 1 (Reel 50)
    Box 75: Folder 3. December, 1963
  - President D.J. McDonald's speeches, 1963-1964; 2 (Reel 50)
    Box 75: Folder 4. December, 1963-April, 1964
  - General, 1963; 3 (Reel 50)
    Box 75: Folder 5. Undated
  - Clippings, 1963; 4 (Reel 50)
    Box 76: Folder 1.
  - General, 1964; 5 (Reel 50)
    Box 76: Folder 2. January-April, 1964
  - The Clergy Economic Education Foundation, 1964; 6 (Reel 50)
    Box 76: Folder 3. March-June, 1964
  - General, 1964; 7 (Reel 50)
    Box 76: Folder 4. May, 1964
  - United Steelworkers Legislative Manual, 1964; 8 (Reel 50)
    Box 77: Folder 1. May, 1964
  - General, 1964; 9 (Reel 50)
    Box 77: Folder 2. June, 1964
- Jun 1964 to Ohio State Univ Labor Advisory Comm, 1964 (Reel 51)
  - United Steelworkers' Institute, Indiana University, 1964; 1 (Reel 51)
    Box 77: Folder 3. June 18-24, 1964
  - General, 1964; 2 (Reel 51)
    Box 77: Folder 4. July, 1964
  - General, 1964; 3 (Reel 51)
    Box 77: Folder 5. August, 1964
  - General, 1964; 4 (Reel 51)
    Box 78: Folder 1. September, 1964
  - General, 1964; 5 (Reel 51)
    Box 78: Folder 2. October-November, 1964
  - General, 1964; 6 (Reel 51)
    Box 78: Folder 3. December, 1964
  - General, 1964; 7 (Reel 51)
    Box 78: Folder 4. Undated
  - Ohio State University Labor Advisory Committee, 1964; 8 (Reel 51)
    Box 78: Folder 5.
- 1964 clippings to 1946-1951 undated items (Reel 52)
  - Clippings, 1964; 1 (Reel 52)
    Box 79: Folder 1.
  - General, 1965; 2 (Reel 52)
    Box 79: Folder 2. January-February, 1965
  - General, 1965; 3 (Reel 52)
    Box 79: Folder 3. March-April, 1965
  - General, 1965; 4 (Reel 52)
    Box 79: Folder 4. May, 1964
  - Boy Scouts, 1965; 5 (Reel 52)
    Box 79: Folder 5.
  - Clippings, 1965; 6 (Reel 52)
    Box 80: Folder 1.
  - Clippings, 7 (Reel 52)
    Box 80: Folder 2. Undated
  - Undated items, 1936-1946; 8 (Reel 52)
    Box 80: Folder 3.
  - Undated items, 1946-1951; 9 (Reel 52)
    Box 80: Folder 4.
- 1951-1965 undated items to Jay B. Krane's papers, 1959 (Reel 53)
  - Undated items, 1951-1965; 1 (Reel 53)
    Box 81: Folder 1.
  - Printed material - samples of Cope-marked and annotated items, 2 (Reel 53)
    Box 81: Folder 2.
  - Jay B. Krane's papers, 1959; 3 (Reel 53)
    Box 81: Folder 3.
- Jay B. Krane's papers Jan 1960 to May 1961 (Reel 54)
  - Jay B. Krane's papers, 1960; 1 (Reel 54)
    Box 82: Folder 1. January-July, 1960
  - Jay B. Krane's papers, 1960; 2 (Reel 54)
    Box 82: Folder 2. August-September, 1960
  - Jay B. Krane's papers, 1960; 3 (Reel 54)
    Box 82: Folder 3. October-December, 1960
  - Jay B. Krane's papers, 1961; 4 (Reel 54)
    Box 82: Folder 4. January-May, 1961
- Guide and Inventory booklets (Reel 55)